Piers Anthony Papers
Piers Anthony Papers
- Writings
  - Short stories
    - Southern Approach [original title: The Bridge], drafts and typescript manuscript (Box 31)
    - Spellroid, summary notes, 1st draft, 3 typescript manuscripts (Box 31)
    - Strappado, notes and story summary, drafts and typescript manuscript (Box 31)
    - Tappuah, notes, holograph draft, numerous versions of typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - 10,000 Mile Check, holograph, preliminary draft and typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - Terror on Planet X (writing as "Piers Jacob"), typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - The Toaster, 2 typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - University, holograph 1st draft, typescript 2nd draft, "1st carbon" and "2nd carbon" typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - Up Schist Crick, holograph and 4 typescript manuscripts, some revised; also includes letter of critique from David Gerrold regarding this piece, which Anthony was planning to use in an upcoming anthology being put together by Gerrold (Box 32)
    - The Value of a Man [later titled: "In the Jaws of Danger"], notes, holograph draft, "intermediate draft" and typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - What Is Time? (writing as Piers Jacob), "supplement to the Milford discussion"; typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - The Whole Truth [original title: "Not That Good"], holograph and typescript manuscript, "1st carbon" typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - Wolf [earlier title: "The Fourth Vampire"], typescript manuscript and revisions (Box 32)
    - Wood You?, holograph and typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - Xanthe's Heart, holograph and 4 typescript manuscript (Box 32)
    - Yoga, notes, holograph manuscript, "working draft", "2nd interim draft", "3rd interim draft", and 2 typescript manuscript; also includes correspondence with Scott DeGarmo (editor at The Floridian, where this story was being written for a 1973 article) and Charlotte Rudeau (yoga instructor used as a resource during the writing of article) (Box 32)
    - [untitled], 1969; notes and holograph manuscript od an introduction to an anthology of Piers Anthony's short stories (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 32)
  - Writings by others
    - Margroff, Robert E., short stories, miscellaneous (Box 33)
    - Offutt, Andrew, short stories, miscellaneous (Box 33)
    - Tiedman, Richard, essay on Jack Vance (Box 33)
- Memorabilia
  - Biographical material (Box 32)
  - Goddard College (Box 32)
  - Journals, 1951-1953; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 32)